(Howard:)...I'm the only one making any real-world
contribution to science and technology.
(Raj:)He's right. This is an important
achievement for two reasons:
(Raj:)Number one, and of course, number two.
[LAUGHING]
(Sheldon:)Oh, clever.
(Sheldon:)Playing on the use of cardinal numbers
as euphemisms for bodily functions.
[LAUGHS]
(Stuart:)Here, Sheldon.
I pulled the new Hellboy for you.
(Stuart:)It's mind-blowing.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, spoiler alert.
But I didn't spoil anything.
(Sheldon:)You told me it's mind-blowing,
so my mind is going into it pre-blown.
(Sheldon:)And once a mind is pre-blown,
it cannot be re-blown.
(Leonard:)- I'm sorry.
- Said the Grinch to Christmas.
- Hey, can I talk to you about something?
- Sure. What's up?
Remember I went out with Penny
a couple weeks ago?
- Yeah, vaguely.
- Sure, you remember. That was the night...
(Raj:)...you went to the bar and made a fool of
yourself trying to pick up strange women.